<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pay_card">ISP / App card payment</string>
    <string name="request_pw_option">1 special character within 8 to 30 characters</string>
    <string name="add">+ add</string>
    <string name="delivery_cost_default">+ 3000 won</string>
    <string name="register_notice_explain">You can sign up as a member by entering the terms of use, consent to the privacy policy, and a certain form of subscription through the [Membership Registration] menu, and you can use the service for free as soon as you sign up. You do not have to enter all the information you need to enter when placing an order. You can always participate in joint purchases and auction events. You can participate in events and various discount events for members.</string>
    <string name="privacy_handle_agree_explain">** This form is a form provided as a sample to help the operation of the shopping mall, and needs to be modified according to the type of shopping mall operation. Before applying it to the shopping mall, please check the operation details of the shopping mall and use it by reflecting the appropriate contents. ** ○○○ Co., Ltd. values your personal information and complies with related laws and regulations such as the Personal Information Protection Act. Through the personal information processing policy, the company will inform you of the purpose and method of using the personal information provided by customers and what measures are being taken to protect personal information. ■ Personal information items to collect and how to collect them A. Items of personal information collected o The company collects the following personal information for membership registration, consultation, and service application. – When registering as a member: Name, date of birth, gender, login ID, password, home phone number, mobile phone number, e–mail, information of legal representative for subscribers under the age of 14 - When applying for service: Address, payment information o Service usage records, access logs, cookies, access IPs, payment records, and defective usage records may be generated and collected during service use or business processing. B. Collection method - Homepage, written form, bulletin board, e-mail, event application, delivery request, phone, fax, collection through generation information collection tool ■ Purpose of collection and use of personal information The company uses the collected personal information for the following purposes. o Implementation of contracts for service provision and settlement of fees for service provision Content provision, purchase and charge payment, shipment of goods or billing destinations, financial transaction identity authentication, and financial services. o Member management Identification, personal identification, prevention of unauthorized use of rogue members, confirmation of intention to sign up, age, confirmation of consent of legal representative when collecting personal information for children under 14 years of age, handling complaints, and delivering notices. o Used in marketing and advertising Statistics on the delivery of advertising information such as events, identification of access frequency, or use of services by members ■ Retention and use period of personal information In principle, after the purpose of collecting and using personal information is achieved, the information is destroyed without delay. However, the following information shall be retained for the period specified for the following reasons: A. Reasons for holding information according to the company\'s internal policy Even if a member withdraws, the member\'s information may be retained for OO years from the date of termination of the contract to prevent the recurrence of illegal use of defective members, settle disputes, and cooperate at the request of the investigative agency. B. Reasons for holding information under relevant laws and regulations If it is necessary to preserve it in accordance with the provisions of relevant laws and regulations, such as the Consumer Protection Act in e-commerce, etc., the company shall keep member information for a certain period of time as prescribed by the relevant laws and regulations as follows. o Records of withdrawal of contracts or subscriptions, etc. - Reason for preservation: Consumer protection in e-commerce, etc. Act - Preservation period: 5 years o Records of payment and supply of goods, etc. - Reasons for preservation: Consumer protection in e-commerce, etc. Act - Preservation period: 5 years o Records of consumer complaints or dispute settlement - Reason for preservation: Consumer protection in e-commerce, etc. Act - Preservation period: 3 years o Logging - Reason for preservation: Communications Secret Protection Act - Storage period: 3 months ■ Procedures and methods for destroying personal information In principle, the company destroys the information without delay after the purpose of collecting and using personal information is achieved. Revocation procedures and methods are as follows. o Revocation procedure The information you enter for membership, etc. will be transferred to a separate DB after the purpose is achieved (separate document box for paper) and stored for a certain period of time (refer to retention and usage period) according to internal policies and other relevant laws. Personal information transferred to a separate DB is not used for any purpose other than being retained unless it is under law. o Destruction method Personal information stored in an electronic file format is deleted using technical methods that cannot be played back. ■ Provide personal information In principle, the company does not provide the user\'s personal information to the outside world. However, exceptions are made in the following cases. o If users agree in advance o Where there is a request from an investigative agency in accordance with the provisions of laws and regulations or in accordance with the procedures and methods prescribed by laws and regulations for investigation purposes; ■ Consignment of collected personal information The company has entrusted the service to an external specialized company as follows. o Consignment target: [Delivery company name] o Contents of consignment work: [Content of consignment to courier] o Subject to consignment: [PG company name] o Contents of consignment work: [Content of consignment to PG company] o Consignee : View supplier list o Contents of entrusted work: [Content of entrusted work]  Rights of users and legal representatives and the method of exercise thereof o Users can inquire or modify their registered personal information at any time and request cancellation of their subscription. o To cancel the subscription (withdrawal of consent) to change personal information (or modify member information) to inquire or modify users\' personal information, click on withdrawal of membership and go through the identification process before viewing, correction, or withdrawal. o If you contact the person in charge of personal information protection in writing, telephone or e-mail, we will take action without delay. o If you request correction for errors in personal information, we will not use or provide the personal information until the correction is completed. In addition, if the wrong personal information has already been provided to a third party, we will notify the third party of the result of correction without delay so that the correction can be made. o The company processes personal information revoked or deleted at the request of the user as specified in the retention and use period of personal information collected by the company and prevents it from being viewed or used for other purposes. ■ Matters concerning the installation, operation, and refusal of automatic personal information collection devices; The company operates cookies that store and find your information from time to time. Cookies are very small text files that the server used to run the website sends to your browser and are stored on your computer\'s hard disk. The company uses cookies for the following purposes: o Purpose of use of cookies, etc. 1. Target marketing and personalized services are provided by analyzing the frequency of access and visit times of members and non-members, identifying user preferences and interests, tracking traces, and identifying the degree of participation in various events and visits. 2. You have the option of installing cookies. Therefore, you can allow all cookies by setting options in your web browser, go through confirmation each time the cookies are saved, or refuse to save all cookies. o How to reject cookie settings 1. As a way to reject cookie settings, you can allow all cookies by selecting the option of your web browser, check each time you save cookies, or refuse to save all cookies. 2. Example of setting method (in the case of Internet Explorer): Tools > Internet Options > Personal Information at the top of the web browser 3. However, if you refuse to install cookies, it may be difficult to provide the service. ■ Complaint service on personal information In order to protect customers\' personal information and handle complaints related to personal information, the company designates related departments and personal information protection managers as follows. o Person in charge of personal information protection Name: OOO Belonging to: OOO Phone number: OO-OO-OOOO Email: o Person in charge of personal information protection Name: OOO Belonging to: OOO Phone number: OO-OO-OOOO Email: o You may report any personal information protection-related complaints arising from the use of the company\'s services to the person in charge of personal information protection or the department in charge. o The company will quickly and fully respond to users\' reports. o If you need to report or consult about other personal information infringement, please contact the institution below. Personal Information Infringement Report Center (privacy.kisa.or.kr / 118 without national number) Personal Information Dispute Mediation Committee (kopico.go.kr / 1833-6972) Cyber Investigation Division of Supreme Prosecutors\' Office (spo.go.kr / Area Code+1301) National Police Agency Cybersecurity Bureau (cyberbureau.police.go.kr / 182 without station number)</string>
    <string name="detail_agree_2">** This form is a form provided as a sample to help the operation of the shopping mall, and needs to be modified according to the type of shopping mall operation. Before applying it to the shopping mall, please check the operation details of the shopping mall and use it by reflecting the appropriate contents. ** 1. Purpose of collection and use of personal information A. Performance of contracts for service provision and settlement of fees for service provision Content provision, purchase and charge payment, shipment of goods or billing destinations, financial transaction identity authentication, and financial services. B. Member management Identification, personal identification, prevention of unauthorized use of rogue members, confirmation of intention to sign up, age, confirmation of consent of legal representative when collecting personal information for children under 14 years of age, handling complaints, and delivering notices. 2. Personal information items to collect: Name, date of birth, gender, login ID, password, home phone number, mobile phone number, e-mail, information of legal representative for subscribers under the age of 14 3. Retention period and usage period of personal information In principle, after the purpose of collecting and using personal information is achieved, the information is destroyed without delay. However, the following information shall be retained for the period specified for the following reasons: A. Reasons for holding information according to the company\'s internal policy o Prevention of fraudulent transactions and storage in accordance with the shopping mall operation policy: OO B. Reasons for holding information under relevant laws and regulations o Records of withdrawal of contracts or subscriptions, etc. - Reason for preservation: Consumer protection in e-commerce, etc. Act - Preservation period: 5 years o Records of payment and supply of goods, etc. - Reasons for preservation: Consumer protection in e-commerce, etc. Act - Preservation period: 5 years o Records of consumer complaints or dispute settlement - Reason for preservation: Consumer protection in e-commerce, etc. Act - Preservation period: 3 years o Logging - Reason for preservation: Communications Secret Protection Act - Storage period: 3 months ※ You can refuse to agree, but if you refuse, you cannot sign up.</string>
    <string name="delivery_notice_explain">- All products are produced after payment has been completed, so delivery will take place on the same day or up to 2 days after the order is placed. \n- There is a limit to daily production when ordering in bulk, so please take your time and contact us before ordering.</string>
    <string name="delivery_etc_explain">- Due to the nature of handmade products, the size may not be constant, and depending on the monitor settings, there may be some differences from the actual color.\n- All products from Palace Confectionery are safe and well-tested products that can be eaten with confidence.</string>
    <string name="delivery_post_explain">- Nationwide delivery product: This product can be delivered nationwide by courier.\n- Shipping costs for all products may vary by product. (Basic shipping fee KRW 3,000) (Some islands and mountainous areas may incur additional costs such as airfare, ferry fare, etc.</string>
    <string name="delivery_gwangju_explain">- Cake and bread products can only be delivered within Gwangju Metropolitan City. (However, except for high-tech, Hanam, Via, and Pyeongdong Industrial Complex areas) - Classroom delivery in school is not possible due to class delays. - Delivery is available from 10 a.m. to 5 p.m. The minimum order amount is 22,000 won. (Can\'t order less than KRW 22,000 / Shipping fee KRW 3,000)</string>
    <string name="change_recall_notice_explain">- Exchanges and returns caused by negligence of the seller will be processed free of charge.\n(In case of incorrect delivery, non-delivery, damage, or defect, request within 24 hours of receipt)\n- Due to the nature of this product, it is not possible to exchange or refund due to the customer\'s simple change of mind after delivery is complete.\n- If the delivered product is deteriorated or has a problem, we will exchange or refund it after determining whether there is negligence or not.\n(Photography required)\n- Before exchanging/returning, you must submit a request to the Customer Center (062-222-3477) for smooth processing.\n- Exchanges and returns are not possible in the following cases.\n① If the product is lost or damaged due to reasons attributable to the buyer\n② If the packaging is opened or the packaging is damaged and the value of the product is lost\n③ In case of exchange or return due to change of mind of the buyer (dispose of the entire product when collecting the product)\n④ In case of misdelivery or non-receipt due to incorrect input of shipping information</string>
    <string name="change_recall_address_explain">- [61482] Palace Confectionery Chungjang Branch, 93-6 Chungjang-ro, Dong-gu, Gwangju (Chungjang-ro 1-ga)</string>
    <string name="delivery_gwangju">&lt;Delivery to Gwangju&gt;</string>
    <string name="delivery_etc">&lt;Other precautions&gt;</string>
    <string name="delivery_notice_cramps">&lt;Delivery information&gt;</string>
    <string name="privacy">Personal information</string>
    <string name="privacy_handle_agree_no_arrow">Personal Information Handling Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_handle_agree">Personal Information Handling Policy ></string>
    <string name="agree_2_title">Consent to collect and use personal information</string>
    <string name="agree_2">Consent to collect and use personal information [Required]</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="no_search">No search results found.</string>
    <string name="pay_method">Payment method</string>
    <string name="pay_detail">Payment details</string>
    <string name="pay_notice">Payment information</string>
    <string name="pay">Paying</string>
    <string name="pay_transfer">account transfer</string>
    <string name="pay_notice_explain">For your safety, the credit card company may give you a confirmation call. If it is determined that the order is not a normal order, such as the use of a stolen card or an order in someone else\'s name, the order may be arbitrarily placed on hold or\n\nFor deposit without a bankbook, you can deposit the product directly from PC banking, Internet banking, telebanking, or a nearby bank.\nThe name of the depositor entered at the time of order must match the name of the actual depositor, and the deposit must be made within 7 days, and orders that have not been deposited will be automatically canceled.</string>
    <string name="favorite">Product of interest</string>
    <string name="empty_favorite">There are no product details of interest.</string>
    <string name="change">Exchange</string>
    <string name="change_and_recall_info_no_arrow">Exchange and Return Information</string>
    <string name="change_and_recall_info">Exchange and Return Information ></string>
    <string name="change_recall_notice">Exchange and Return Guide</string>
    <string name="change_recall_address">Exchange and Return Address</string>
    <string name="delivery_default">Basic Shipping</string>
    <string name="delivery_default_address">Basic Shipping Destination</string>
    <string name="etc">etc</string>
    <string name="etc_notice">Other Information</string>
    <string name="age">age</string>
    <string name="select_age">Please choose your age.</string>
    <string name="content">content</string>
    <string name="next">next</string>
    <string name="just_cancel">a simple change of mind</string>
    <string name="enroll">Registration</string>
    <string name="enroll_do_it">Registering</string>
    <string name="logout">Sign out</string>
    <string name="login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="go_login">On the Sign in screen.</string>
    <string name="login_comment">Buy delicious palace confectionery breads!</string>
    <string name="sell_shop">store sales</string>
    <string name="qa">Inquiry</string>
    <string name="qa_do_it">Inquiry Us</string>
    <string name="direct_pay">Buy it right away.</string>
    <string name="recall">Return</string>
    <string name="delivery_and_payment_info_no_arrow">Shipping and Product Payment Information</string>
    <string name="delivery_and_payment_info">Shipping and Product Payment Information ></string>
    <string name="delivery_cost">The delivery charge</string>
    <string name="finish_delivery">Delivery completed</string>
    <string name="delivery_info">Shipping information</string>
    <string name="ing_delivery">Delivery in progress</string>
    <string name="delivery_notice">Delivery Information</string>
    <string name="ready_delivery">Preparing for delivery</string>
    <string name="order_address">Shipping destination</string>
    <string name="set_order_address">Shipping destination registration</string>
    <string name="change_order_address">Delivery destination change</string>
    <string name="setting_order_address">Shipping settings</string>
    <string name="delivery_option">Delivery method: Delivery\nDelivery Region: National Region\nShipping cost: KRW 3,000\nDelivery period: 3–7 days</string>
    <string name="storage">Storage method</string>
    <string name="have_coupon">Retained coupon</string>
    <string name="stay_screen">While maintaining the main screen, the palace confectionery booth\nWe\'ll give you a small gift if you visit!</string>
    <string name="aging">decay or degeneration</string>
    <string name="change_pw">Your password has been changed.</string>
    <string name="re_pw_wrong">Passwords do not match.</string>
    <string name="request_pw">Please enter your password.</string>
    <string name="request_re_pw">Please enter your password one more time.</string>
    <string name="pw_wrong_option">Password must contain between 8 and 30 characters and one special character.</string>
    <string name="find_pw">Find a password</string>
    <string name="change_pw_explain">Your password has been changed.\nPlease log in with a new password.</string>
    <string name="re_pw_no_star">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="re_pw">Confirm Password *</string>
    <string name="pw">Password *</string>
    <string name="bread">Bread</string>
    <string name="size">Size</string>
    <string name="image">Picture</string>
    <string name="select_image">Select a picture</string>
    <string name="detail_info">Detailed information</string>
    <string name="detail_order_address">Detailed address</string>
    <string name="request_detail_order_address">Please enter a detailed address.</string>
    <string name="select_first_option">Please select the top option first.</string>
    <string name="pay_info">Product payment information</string>
    <string name="item_question">Product inquiry</string>
    <string name="all_item_question">View all Product inquiries</string>
    <string name="request_item_quality">Please write down the evaluation of the product.</string>
    <string name="request_item_question">Please let me know if you have any questions about the product.</string>
    <string name="item_info">Product information</string>
    <string name="order_notice_explain">The product order is made in the following steps.\n\n- Step 1: Product search\n- Step 2: Put it in your shopping cart.\n- Step 3: Log in to a member ID or order a non-member.\n- Step 4: Create an Order\n- Step 5: Select payment method and pay\n- Step6: Order Success Screen (Order Number)\n\nIf it is a non-membership order, please take note of the order number and approval number (when paying by card) in step 6. However, if you are a member, you do not need to manage it separately because it is automatically saved.</string>
    <string name="item_review">Product review</string>
    <string name="all_item_review">View the entire product review</string>
    <string name="item_price">commodity prices</string>
    <string name="new_pw">New Password</string>
    <string name="request_new_pw">Please enter a new password.</string>
    <string name="present">as a gift</string>
    <string name="select">Choice</string>
    <string name="select_delete">Delete Selection</string>
    <string name="no_select">No choice</string>
    <string name="ingredient">Ingredient</string>
    <string name="terminate_condition_notice">Extinction condition</string>
    <string name="agree_3_title">Agree to receive shopping information</string>
    <string name="agree_3">Agree to receive shopping information [Select]</string>
    <string name="amount">Quantity</string>
    <string name="edit">crystal</string>
    <string name="stamp">stamp</string>
    <string name="id_no_star">ID</string>
    <string name="copied_id">The ID has been copied to the clipboard.</string>
    <string name="request_id">Please enter your ID.</string>
    <string name="find_id">Find your ID.</string>
    <string name="login_wrong">The IDs or passwords do not match.</string>
    <string name="id">ID *</string>
    <string name="none_review">There is no product review yet.</string>
    <string name="none_qa">There are no product inquiries yet.</string>
    <string name="allergy">Allergy information</string>
    <string name="change_option">Change options</string>
    <string name="select_option">Please select an option.</string>
    <string name="complicate">Completion</string>
    <string name="size_too_small">Capacity not reached</string>
    <string name="expiration_date">Distribution period</string>
    <string name="date_expired">expiration of validity</string>
    <string name="select_already_option">This option is already selected.</string>
    <string name="already_shopping_list">It\'s already in the shopping cart.</string>
    <string name="name_no_star">Name</string>
    <string name="request_name">Please enter your name.</string>
    <string name="name">Name *</string>
    <string name="email_no_star">Email</string>
    <string name="request_email">Please enter your email.</string>
    <string name="email_wrong">Please enter it according to the email format.</string>
    <string name="email">Email *</string>
    <string name="mix_other">foreign substance incorporation</string>
    <string name="id_already">This ID already exists.</string>
    <string name="email_already">This email already exists.</string>
    <string name="etc_notice_explain">Period of use\nThe reserve generated by the order will not be converted into the actual available reserve until 20 days after the delivery completion check. It is classified as an unused reserve for 20 days. Unavailable reserves are reserves for orders that have not been actually purchased in preparation for returns, cancellations, etc.\nAvailable reserves (total reserves - used reserves - unused reserves) can be used immediately when purchasing the product.</string>
    <string name="information_use_no_arrow">Usage Information</string>
    <string name="information_use">Usage Information ></string>
    <string name="terms_of_services_no_arrow">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="agree_1_title">Acceptance of Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="agree_1">Acceptance of Terms and Conditions [Required]</string>
    <string name="terms_of_services">Terms and Conditions ></string>
    <string name="use_condition_notice">Terms of use</string>
    <string name="certify">Authentication number</string>
    <string name="certify_expired">The authentication number has expired.</string>
    <string name="certify_wrong">The authentication numbers do not match.</string>
    <string name="request_certify">Please enter the authentication number.</string>
    <string name="certify_re_send">Resend authentication number</string>
    <string name="certified">Authenticating</string>
    <string name="delay_delivery">Receiving delay</string>
    <string name="detail_agree">Read more ></string>
    <string name="shopping_list">shopping basket</string>
    <string name="empty_shopping_list">There are no items in the shopping cart.</string>
    <string name="add_shopping_list">I added it to my shopping cart.</string>
    <string name="save">Storage</string>
    <string name="use_condition_notice_explain">When using reserves, the minimum purchaseable reserve (purchaseable reserve requirement) is 3,000 won. When using the reserve, the maximum purchaseable reserve (maximum amount of the reserve available once) is \'no limit\'.</string>
    <string name="phone_wrong">Please enter it according to the phone number format.</string>
    <string name="all">the entire</string>
    <string name="all_agree">All agreements</string>
    <string name="delete_all">Delete all</string>
    <string name="select_all">Select All</string>
    <string name="detail_agree_1">Article 1 (Purpose)\nThese terms and conditions are the rights of cyber malls and users in using Internet-related services (hereinafter referred to as "services") provided by the Palace Confectionery Cyber Mall (hereinafter referred to as "mall") operated by the Palace Confectionery (e-commerce operator).The purpose is to define obligations and responsibilities.\n「 These terms and conditions shall apply mutatis mutandis to e-commerce using PC communication, wireless, etc., unless they are contrary to their nature.」\nArticle 2 (Definitions)\n① The term "mall" means a virtual business place where palace confectionery can trade goods, etc. using information and communication facilities such as computers to provide goods or services (hereinafter referred to as "goods, etc.) to users, and it is also used as a business operator of a cyber mall.\n② The term "user" means members and non-members who access "Mall" and receive services provided by "Mall" under these terms and conditions.\n③ The term "member" means a person who has registered as a member of the "Mall" and who can continuously use the services provided by the "Mall".\n④ The term "non-member" means a person who does not sign up for membership and uses the services provided by the "Mall".\nArticle 3 (Specification, explanation, and revision of the terms and conditions, etc.)\n① "Mall" means the content of these terms and conditions, the trade name and the name of the representative, the address of the place of business (including the address of the place where consumers can handle complaints), and the telephone number.Post the simulated transmission number, e-mail address, business registration number, mail order business report number, and personal information protection manager on the initial service screen (front) of 00 Cyber Mall so that users can easily know. However, the contents of the terms and conditions can be viewed by the user through the connection screen.\n② "Mall is withdrawal of subscription among the contents stipulated in the terms and conditions before the user agrees to the terms and conditions.A separate connection screen or pop-up screen should be provided to the user so that the user can understand important contents such as delivery responsibility and refund conditions.\n③ "Mall" may amend these terms and conditions to the extent that it does not violate related laws such as the Consumer Protection Act in Electronic Commerce, the Framework Act on Electronic Documents and Electronic Transactions, the Electronic Signatures Act, the Act on Promotion and Information Protection, etc.\n④ If "Mall" revises the terms and conditions, it shall be announced on the initial screen of the mall from 7 days before the application date to the day before the application date, specifying the date of application and the reason for the revision. However, if the terms and conditions are changed against the user, a minimum grace period of 30 days will be announced. In this case, "Mall" clearly compares the content before and after the revision and displays it for users to understand.\n⑤ If "Mall" amends the terms and conditions, the revised terms and conditions apply only to contracts concluded after the date of application, and the terms and conditions before the amendment apply to contracts already made before that date. However, if a user who has already signed a contract sends his/her intention to be subject to the revised terms and conditions to "Mall" within the notice period of the revised terms and conditions under paragraph 3 and obtains consent from "Mall", the revised terms and conditions shall apply.\n⑥ Matters not prescribed in these terms and conditions and interpretations of these terms shall be governed by the Consumer Protection Act in e-commerce, the Regulation of Terms, etc., the Consumer Protection Guidelines and related laws or commercial regulations in e-commerce set by the Fair Trade Commission.\nArticle 4 (Provision and Change of Services)\n① "Mall" does the following:\n1. Provision of information on goods or services and conclusion of a purchase contract\n2. Delivery of goods or services to which a purchase contract has been concluded\n3. Other duties prescribed by "Mall"\n② "Mall" may change the contents of goods or services to be provided under a contract concluded in the future in the event of a loss of goods or services or a change in technical specifications. In this case, the contents of the changed goods or services and the date of provision shall be specified and the contents of the current goods or services shall be immediately announced to the place where they are posted.\n③ If the contents of the service contracted with the user to be provided by the "Mall" are changed due to reasons such as sold out of goods, etc. or changes in technical specifications, the reason shall be notified to the user immediately.\n④ In the case of the preceding paragraph, "Mall" compensates the user for damages caused by this. However, this is not the case if "mol" proves that there is no intention or negligence.\nArticle 5 (Discontinuance of Service)\n① "Mall" means maintenance and inspection of information and communication facilities such as computers.In the event of a replacement, failure, or loss of communication, the provision of the service may be temporarily suspended.\n② "Mall" shall compensate the user or a third party for damages caused by the temporary suspension of the service due to the reason under paragraph (1). However, this is not the case if "mol" proves that it is not intentional or negligent.\n③ "Mall" shall notify the user in the manner prescribed in Article 8 and compensate the consumer according to the conditions originally stated in "Mall" if the service cannot be provided due to the conversion of business items, abandonment of business, or integration among businesses. However, if the "Mall" does not notify the compensation standards, etc., the mileage or reserves of the users shall be paid to the users in kind or cash corresponding to the currency value used in the "Mall".\nArticle 6 (Membership registration)\n① Users apply for membership by filling in their membership information according to the subscription form set by "Mall" and expressing their consent to these terms and conditions.\n② The "Mall" shall be registered as a member unless it falls under any of the following subparagraphs among users who have applied for membership as in paragraph (1):\n1. Where an applicant has previously lost his membership pursuant to Article 7 (3) of this Agreement, this shall not apply where he/she has obtained consent to rejoin "Mall" three years after the loss of membership under Article 7 (3).\n2. If there is a false, omission, or error in the registration content.\n3. Where it is deemed that registering as a member is significantly hindered by the technology of "Mall".\n③ The time when the membership contract is established is when the consent of "Mall" reaches the member.\n④ If there is a change in the matters registered at the time of membership, a member shall notify the "mall" of the change within a considerable period of time by modifying member information, etc.\nArticle 7 (Membership withdrawal and loss of qualification, etc.)\n① Members may request withdrawal from "Mall" at any time, and "Mall" will process withdrawal immediately.\n② Where a member falls under any of the following reasons, "Mall" may restrict and suspend his/her membership:\n1. When false information is registered at the time of application for membership.\n2. Where the payment of goods, etc. purchased using the "mall" or other debts borne by the member related to the use of the "mall" are not paid on the date.\n3. In the case of threatening the e-commerce order, such as interfering with the use of other people\'s "mall" or stealing the information;\n4. In the case of using "mall" to prohibit laws or these terms and conditions or to act contrary to public morals.\n③ "Mall" restricts membership.After suspension, if the same act is repeated more than twice or the reason is not corrected within 30 days, "Mall" may lose its membership.\n④ If "Mall" loses its membership, the membership registration will be canceled. In this case, the members shall be notified of this and given an opportunity to explain for a period of at least 30 days before the cancellation of the membership registration.\nArticle 8 (Notice to Members)\n① If "Mall" gives notice to a member, it may be made to the e-mail address designated by the member in advance by "Mall".\n② "Mall" can be substituted for individual notifications by posting them on the "Mall" bulletin board for more than one week for notifications to an unspecified number of members. However, individual notifications are made for matters that have a significant impact on the member\'s own transaction.\nArticle 9 (Application for Purchase)\n① The "Mall" user shall apply for purchase on the "Mall" by the following or similar means, and the "Mall" shall provide the following information in an easy-to-understand manner when the user applies for purchase:\n1. Search and select goods, etc.\n2. Enter the recipient\'s name, address, phone number, e-mail address (or mobile phone number), etc.\n3. Contents of terms and conditions, services with limited subscription withdrawal rights, and delivery fees.Confirmation of the contents related to the burden of installation costs, etc.\n4. Indication that you agree to these terms and conditions and confirm or reject the matters in paragraph 3. above (e.g., mouse click)\n5. Consent to the application for purchase of goods, etc. and confirmation thereof or confirmation of "mall"\n6. Selection of payment method\n② If "Mall" needs to provide and entrust the buyer\'s personal information to a third party, it must obtain the buyer\'s consent when applying for the actual purchase, and it does not receive comprehensive consent in advance when registering as a member. At this time, the "Mall" shall specify to the buyer the items of personal information provided, the recipient, the purpose of using the personal information of the recipient, the period of retention and use, etc. However, if there are other provisions in the relevant statutes, such as entrustment of personal information processing under Article 25 (1) of the Information and Communication Network Utilization Promotion and Information Protection, etc. Act, etc., it shall apply.\nArticle 10 (Conclusion of Contract)\n① "Mall" may refuse to accept a purchase application under Article 9 if it falls under any of the following subparagraphs: However, in the case of signing a contract with a minor, the minor himself or the legal representative must notify that the contract can be canceled if the consent of the legal representative is not obtained.\n1. If there is a false, omission, or error in the application.\n2. When a minor purchases goods and services prohibited by the Youth Protection Act, such as cigarettes and alcohol.\n3. Where it is determined that accepting other purchase applications is significantly hindered by "mall" technology.\n② The contract shall be deemed to have been concluded when the consent of "Mall" reaches the user in the form of a notification of receipt under Article 12 (1).\n③ The expression of consent of "Mall" shall include information on the confirmation of the user\'s purchase application, availability of sales, cancellation of correction of the purchase application, etc.\nArticle 11 (Payment Method)\nThe payment method for goods or services purchased in the "Mall" may be made by any of the following methods: However, "Mall" cannot be collected by adding any nominal fee to the payment of goods, etc. for the user\'s payment method.\n1. Transfer of various accounts such as phone banking, Internet banking, mail banking, etc.\n2. Payment by various cards such as prepaid cards, debit cards, credit cards, etc.\n3. Online deposit without a bankbook\n4. Payment by electronic money\n5. Payment upon receipt\n6. Payment by points paid by "Mall" such as mileage\n7. Payment by gift certificate signed with "Mall" or recognized by "Mall"\n8. Payment by other electronic payment methods, etc.\nArticle 12 (Notice of receipt confirmation.Purchase application change and cancellation)\n① "Mall" notifies the user of receipt confirmation when the user requests a purchase.\n② If there is a discrepancy in the expression of intention, the user may request to change or cancel the purchase application immediately after receiving the confirmation notice, and if there is a request from the user before delivery, the "Mall" shall be processed according to the request. However, if the payment has already been made, the provisions on withdrawal of subscription, etc. under Article 15 shall be followed.\nArticle 13 (Supply of Goods, etc.)\n① Unless there is a separate agreement with the user on the timing of supply of goods, etc., "Mall" shall take other necessary measures such as customization, packaging, etc. so that the goods can be delivered within 7 days from the date of subscription. However, if "Mall" has already received all or part of the payment for goods, etc., measures shall be taken within three business days from the date of receipt of all or part of the payment. At this time, "Mall" takes appropriate measures to help users check the supply procedures and progress of goods, etc.\n② "Mall" specifies the means of delivery, the person who bears the shipping cost by means, and the delivery period by means for the goods purchased by the user. If the "mall" exceeds the agreed delivery period, the user shall be compensated for the damage caused by it. But "mol" is intentional.This is not the case if you have proved that you are not culpable.\nArticle 14 (Refund)\n"Mall" shall notify the user of the reason without delay if the goods, etc. requested by the user cannot be delivered or provided due to out of stock, etc., and if the payment is received in advance, refund or take necessary measures for refund within three business days.\nArticle 15 (Revocation of subscription, etc.)\n① A user who has signed a contract with "Mall" on the purchase of goods, etc. may withdraw the subscription within seven days from the date of receipt of a written contract under Article 13 (2) of the Consumer Protection Act in Electronic Commerce, etc. (if the supply of goods, etc. is later than the time of receipt). However, if the withdrawal of subscription is otherwise stipulated in the Consumer Protection Act in Electronic Commerce, etc., the provisions of the same Act shall be followed.\n② When a user receives goods, etc., he/she shall not return or exchange goods in any of the following cases:\n1. Where goods, etc. are lost or damaged due to reasons responsible to the user (However, if the packaging, etc. is damaged to check the contents of goods, etc., the subscription may be withdrawn.)\n2. Where the value of goods, etc. has significantly decreased due to user use or partial consumption.\n3. Where the value of goods, etc. has decreased significantly to the extent that it is difficult to resell over time.\n4. Where the packaging of the original goods, etc. is damaged when reproduction is possible with goods, etc. with the same performance.\n③ In the case of paragraph (2) 2 through 4, the withdrawal of subscription by users is not restricted unless "mall" has been specified in a place where consumers can easily know in advance that the withdrawal of subscription is restricted or measures such as providing trial products are taken.\n④ Notwithstanding paragraphs (1) and (2), if the contents of goods, etc. are different from the contents of the display or advertisement or are implemented differently from the contents of the contract, the user may withdraw the subscription within three months from the date of receiving the goods, etc. or within 30 days from the date of knowing such fact.\nArticle 16 (Effect of withdrawal of subscription, etc.)\n① "Mall" shall refund the amount of goods, etc. already paid within three business days when goods, etc. are returned from the user. In this case, if the "Mall" delays the refund of goods, etc. to the user, the delayed period shall be paid by multiplying the delayed interest rate (deleting the parentheses) prescribed in Article 21-2 of the Enforcement Decree of the Consumer Protection Act on Electronic Commerce, etc.\n② In refunding the above payment, "Mall" requests the business operator who provided the payment method to suspend or cancel the claim for goods, etc. without delay when the user pays for goods, etc. through a payment method such as credit card or electronic money.\n③ In the case of withdrawal of subscription, etc., the user shall bear the expenses necessary for the return of the supplied goods, etc. "Mall" does not claim a penalty or compensation for damages due to withdrawal of subscription. However, if the contents of goods, etc. are different from the contents of the display or advertisement or are implemented differently from the contents of the contract, the "Mall" shall bear the expenses required for the return of goods, etc.\n④ If the user pays the shipping cost when receiving goods, etc., "Mall" clearly indicates who pays the cost when withdrawing the subscription.\nArticle 17 (Personal Information Protection)\n① "Mall" collects minimum personal information to the extent necessary for providing services when collecting personal information of users.\n② "Mall" does not collect information necessary to fulfill the purchase contract in advance when signing up for a member. However, this is not the case when identification is required before the purchase contract in order to fulfill the obligations under related laws and regulations, and the minimum specific personal information is collected.\n③ "Mall" shall notify the relevant user of the purpose and obtain consent when collecting and using the user\'s personal information.\n④ "Mall" shall not use the collected personal information for any purpose other than the purpose, and where a new purpose of use arises or provides it to a third party, the purpose shall be notified to the relevant user and consent shall be obtained at the stage of use and provision. However, exceptions are made if the relevant laws and regulations stipulate otherwise.\n⑤ Where "Mall" requires the consent of the user pursuant to paragraphs (2) and (3), the identity of the person in charge of personal information protection (affiliation, name and phone number, other contact information), information collection and use purpose, and information provision to third parties (information to be provided) shall be withdrawn at any time.\n⑥ The user may request access and error correction of his or her personal information held by the Mall at any time, and the Mall is obligated to take necessary measures without delay. If the user requests correction of the error, "Mall" will not use the personal information until the error is corrected.\n⑦ For the protection of personal information, "Mall" shall limit the number of users who process their personal information to a minimum and shall be responsible for all damages caused by loss, theft, leakage, provision to third parties without consent, and alteration of their personal information, including credit cards and bank accounts.\n⑧ "Mall" or a third party who has received personal information from it shall destroy the personal information without delay when it achieves the purpose of collecting or receiving personal information.\n⑨ "Mall" does not set the consent column for the collection, use, or provision of personal information as selected in advance. In addition, it specifically specifies services restricted when users refuse to consent to collect, use, or provide personal information, and does not restrict or refuse to provide services such as membership registration on the grounds of the user\'s refusal to collect, use, and provide personal information.\nArticle 18 (Obligation of "Mall")\n① "Mall" does not act prohibited by laws and regulations or contrary to public order and customs, and goods are continuously and stably as prescribed by these terms and conditions.We must do our best to provide services.\n② The "Mall" shall have a security system for the protection of users\' personal information (including credit information) so that users can use the Internet service safely.\n③ "Mall" refers to goods or services.Unfair indication prescribed in Article 3 of the Act on Fair Advertising.If a user suffers damage through advertising, he or she is responsible for compensation.\n④ "Mall" does not send for-profit advertising emails that you do not want.\nArticle 19 (Obligation for ID and password of a member)\n① Except in the case of Article 17, the member is responsible for managing the ID and password.\n② Members shall not allow third parties to use their IDs and passwords.\n③ If a member recognizes that his/her ID and password have been stolen or used by a third party, he/she shall notify "Mall" immediately and follow "Mall"\'s instructions.\nArticle 20 (Obligation of Users)\nThe user shall not:\n1. Registration of false information when applying or changing\n2. Stealing information from others\n3. Change of information posted in "Mall"\n4. Transmission or posting of information (computer programs, etc.) other than information prescribed by "Mall"\n5. Infringement of intellectual property rights such as "mall" and other copyrights of third parties\n6. "Mall" or other acts that damage the reputation of third parties or interfere with their work.\n7. Disclosure or posting obscene or violent messages, images, voices, or other information contrary to public morals in the mall.\nArticle 21 (Relationship between the "mall" and the "mall" to be connected)\n① If the parent "mall" and the child "mall" are hyperlinked (such as the target of the hyperlink includes letters, pictures, and fairy tales), the former is called the linked "mall" (website), and the latter is called the connected "mall" (website).\n② The consolidated "mall" shall not be liable for guarantee of transactions with the user by goods, etc. provided by the consolidated "mall", if the initial screen of the consolidated "mall" or the pop-up screen at the time of connection.\nArticle 22 (Restriction on attribution and use of copyright)\n① Copyright and other intellectual property rights to works created by "Mall" belong to "Mall".\n② Users shall not reproduce, transmit, publish, distribute, broadcast, or allow third parties to use the information obtained by using "Mall" for commercial purposes without the prior consent of "Mall".\n③ "Mall" shall notify the user of the copyright attributed to the user in accordance with the agreement.\nArticle 23 (Dispute Resolution)\n① The "Mall" shall establish a damage compensation handling organization to reflect legitimate opinions or complaints raised by the user and compensate for the damage.It\'s in operation.\n② "Mall" handles complaints and comments submitted by users preferentially. However, if it is difficult to process quickly, we will immediately notify the user of the reason and the processing schedule.\n③ If a user applies for damage relief in connection with an e-commerce dispute between a "mall" and a user, it may be subject to mediation by the Fair Trade Commission or a dispute settlement agency commissioned by the city/provincial governor.\nArticle 24 (Judicial Rights and Applicable Acts)\n① A lawsuit concerning an e-commerce dispute between the "mall" and the user shall be subject to the address of the user at the time of filing, and if there is no address, the district court having jurisdiction over the residence shall have exclusive jurisdiction. However, if the user\'s address or residence is not clear at the time of filing the complaint, or if a foreign resident is a foreigner, it is filed with the competent court under the Civil Procedure Act.\n② Korean law applies to e-commerce lawsuits filed between "mall" and users.\nAppendix (Effective Date) These terms and conditions will take effect from the date of the year. Appendix (Effective Date) These terms and conditions will take effect from the date of the year.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_services_explain">Article 1 (Purpose)\nThese terms and conditions are the rights of cyber malls and users in using Internet-related services (hereinafter referred to as "services") provided by the Palace Confectionery Cyber Mall (hereinafter referred to as "mall") operated by the Palace Confectionery (e-commerce operator).The purpose is to define obligations and responsibilities.\n「 These terms and conditions shall apply mutatis mutandis to e-commerce using PC communication, wireless, etc., unless they are contrary to their nature.」\nArticle 2 (Definitions)\n① The term "mall" means a virtual business place where palace confectionery can trade goods, etc. using information and communication facilities such as computers to provide goods or services (hereinafter referred to as "goods, etc.) to users, and it is also used as a business operator of a cyber mall.\n② The term "user" means members and non-members who access "Mall" and receive services provided by "Mall" under these terms and conditions.\n③ The term "member" means a person who has registered as a member of the "Mall" and who can continuously use the services provided by the "Mall".\n④ The term "non-member" means a person who does not sign up for membership and uses the services provided by the "Mall".\nArticle 3 (Specification, explanation, and revision of the terms and conditions, etc.)\n① "Mall" means the content of these terms and conditions, the trade name and the name of the representative, the address of the place of business (including the address of the place where consumers can handle complaints), and the telephone number.Post the simulated transmission number, e-mail address, business registration number, mail order business report number, and personal information protection manager on the initial service screen (front) of 00 Cyber Mall so that users can easily know. However, the contents of the terms and conditions can be viewed by the user through the connection screen.\n② "Mall is withdrawal of subscription among the contents stipulated in the terms and conditions before the user agrees to the terms and conditions.A separate connection screen or pop-up screen should be provided to the user so that the user can understand important contents such as delivery responsibility and refund conditions.\n③ "Mall" may amend these terms and conditions to the extent that it does not violate related laws such as the Consumer Protection Act in Electronic Commerce, the Framework Act on Electronic Documents and Electronic Transactions, the Electronic Signatures Act, the Act on Promotion and Information Protection, etc.\n④ If "Mall" revises the terms and conditions, it shall be announced on the initial screen of the mall from 7 days before the application date to the day before the application date, specifying the date of application and the reason for the revision. However, if the terms and conditions are changed against the user, a minimum grace period of 30 days will be announced. In this case, "Mall" clearly compares the content before and after the revision and displays it for users to understand.\n⑤ If "Mall" amends the terms and conditions, the revised terms and conditions apply only to contracts concluded after the date of application, and the terms and conditions before the amendment apply to contracts already made before that date. However, if a user who has already signed a contract sends his/her intention to be subject to the revised terms and conditions to "Mall" within the notice period of the revised terms and conditions under paragraph 3 and obtains consent from "Mall", the revised terms and conditions shall apply.\n⑥ Matters not prescribed in these terms and conditions and interpretations of these terms shall be governed by the Consumer Protection Act in e-commerce, the Regulation of Terms, etc., the Consumer Protection Guidelines and related laws or commercial regulations in e-commerce set by the Fair Trade Commission.\nArticle 4 (Provision and Change of Services)\n① "Mall" does the following:\n1. Provision of information on goods or services and conclusion of a purchase contract\n2. Delivery of goods or services to which a purchase contract has been concluded\n3. Other duties prescribed by "Mall"\n② "Mall" may change the contents of goods or services to be provided under a contract concluded in the future in the event of a loss of goods or services or a change in technical specifications. In this case, the contents of the changed goods or services and the date of provision shall be specified and the contents of the current goods or services shall be immediately announced to the place where they are posted.\n③ If the contents of the service contracted with the user to be provided by the "Mall" are changed due to reasons such as sold out of goods, etc. or changes in technical specifications, the reason shall be notified to the user immediately.\n④ In the case of the preceding paragraph, "Mall" compensates the user for damages caused by this. However, this is not the case if "mol" proves that there is no intention or negligence.\nArticle 5 (Discontinuance of Service)\n① "Mall" means maintenance and inspection of information and communication facilities such as computers.In the event of a replacement, failure, or loss of communication, the provision of the service may be temporarily suspended.\n② "Mall" shall compensate the user or a third party for damages caused by the temporary suspension of the service due to the reason under paragraph (1). However, this is not the case if "mol" proves that it is not intentional or negligent.\n③ "Mall" shall notify the user in the manner prescribed in Article 8 and compensate the consumer according to the conditions originally stated in "Mall" if the service cannot be provided due to the conversion of business items, abandonment of business, or integration among businesses. However, if the "Mall" does not notify the compensation standards, etc., the mileage or reserves of the users shall be paid to the users in kind or cash corresponding to the currency value used in the "Mall".\nArticle 6 (Membership registration)\n① Users apply for membership by filling in their membership information according to the subscription form set by "Mall" and expressing their consent to these terms and conditions.\n② The "Mall" shall be registered as a member unless it falls under any of the following subparagraphs among users who have applied for membership as in paragraph (1):\n1. Where an applicant has previously lost his membership pursuant to Article 7 (3) of this Agreement, this shall not apply where he/she has obtained consent to rejoin "Mall" three years after the loss of membership under Article 7 (3).\n2. If there is a false, omission, or error in the registration content.\n3. Where it is deemed that registering as a member is significantly hindered by the technology of "Mall".\n③ The time when the membership contract is established is when the consent of "Mall" reaches the member.\n④ If there is a change in the matters registered at the time of membership, a member shall notify the "mall" of the change within a considerable period of time by modifying member information, etc.\nArticle 7 (Membership withdrawal and loss of qualification, etc.)\n① Members may request withdrawal from "Mall" at any time, and "Mall" will process withdrawal immediately.\n② Where a member falls under any of the following reasons, "Mall" may restrict and suspend his/her membership:\n1. When false information is registered at the time of application for membership.\n2. Where the payment of goods, etc. purchased using the "mall" or other debts borne by the member related to the use of the "mall" are not paid on the date.\n3. In the case of threatening the e-commerce order, such as interfering with the use of other people\'s "mall" or stealing the information;\n4. In the case of using "mall" to prohibit laws or these terms and conditions or to act contrary to public morals.\n③ "Mall" restricts membership.After suspension, if the same act is repeated more than twice or the reason is not corrected within 30 days, "Mall" may lose its membership.\n④ If "Mall" loses its membership, the membership registration will be canceled. In this case, the members shall be notified of this and given an opportunity to explain for a period of at least 30 days before the cancellation of the membership registration.\nArticle 8 (Notice to Members)\n① If "Mall" gives notice to a member, it may be made to the e-mail address designated by the member in advance by "Mall".\n② "Mall" can be substituted for individual notifications by posting them on the "Mall" bulletin board for more than one week for notifications to an unspecified number of members. However, individual notifications are made for matters that have a significant impact on the member\'s own transaction.\nArticle 9 (Application for Purchase)\n① The "Mall" user shall apply for purchase on the "Mall" by the following or similar means, and the "Mall" shall provide the following information in an easy-to-understand manner when the user applies for purchase:\n1. Search and select goods, etc.\n2. Enter the recipient\'s name, address, phone number, e-mail address (or mobile phone number), etc.\n3. Contents of terms and conditions, services with limited subscription withdrawal rights, and delivery fees.Confirmation of the contents related to the burden of installation costs, etc.\n4. Indication that you agree to these terms and conditions and confirm or reject the matters in paragraph 3. above (e.g., mouse click)\n5. Consent to the application for purchase of goods, etc. and confirmation thereof or confirmation of "mall"\n6. Selection of payment method\n② If "Mall" needs to provide and entrust the buyer\'s personal information to a third party, it must obtain the buyer\'s consent when applying for the actual purchase, and it does not receive comprehensive consent in advance when registering as a member. At this time, the "Mall" shall specify to the buyer the items of personal information provided, the recipient, the purpose of using the personal information of the recipient, the period of retention and use, etc. However, if there are other provisions in the relevant statutes, such as entrustment of personal information processing under Article 25 (1) of the Information and Communication Network Utilization Promotion and Information Protection, etc. Act, etc., it shall apply.\nArticle 10 (Conclusion of Contract)\n① "Mall" may refuse to accept a purchase application under Article 9 if it falls under any of the following subparagraphs: However, in the case of signing a contract with a minor, the minor himself or the legal representative must notify that the contract can be canceled if the consent of the legal representative is not obtained.\n1. If there is a false, omission, or error in the application.\n2. When a minor purchases goods and services prohibited by the Youth Protection Act, such as cigarettes and alcohol.\n3. Where it is determined that accepting other purchase applications is significantly hindered by "mall" technology.\n② The contract shall be deemed to have been concluded when the consent of "Mall" reaches the user in the form of a notification of receipt under Article 12 (1).\n③ The expression of consent of "Mall" shall include information on the confirmation of the user\'s purchase application, availability of sales, cancellation of correction of the purchase application, etc.\nArticle 11 (Payment Method)\nThe payment method for goods or services purchased in the "Mall" may be made by any of the following methods: However, "Mall" cannot be collected by adding any nominal fee to the payment of goods, etc. for the user\'s payment method.\n1. Transfer of various accounts such as phone banking, Internet banking, mail banking, etc.\n2. Payment by various cards such as prepaid cards, debit cards, credit cards, etc.\n3. Online deposit without a bankbook\n4. Payment by electronic money\n5.Payment upon receipt\n6. Payment by points paid by "Mall" such as mileage\n7. Payment by gift certificate signed with "Mall" or recognized by "Mall"\n8. Payment by other electronic payment methods, etc.\nArticle 12 (Notice of receipt confirmation.Purchase application change and cancellation)\n① "Mall" notifies the user of receipt confirmation when the user requests a purchase.\n② If there is a discrepancy in the expression of intention, the user may request to change or cancel the purchase application immediately after receiving the confirmation notice, and if there is a request from the user before delivery, the "Mall" shall be processed according to the request. However, if the payment has already been made, the provisions on withdrawal of subscription, etc. under Article 15 shall be followed.\nArticle 13 (Supply of Goods, etc.)\n① Unless there is a separate agreement with the user on the timing of supply of goods, etc., "Mall" shall take other necessary measures such as customization, packaging, etc. so that the goods can be delivered within 7 days from the date of subscription. However, if "Mall" has already received all or part of the payment for goods, etc., measures shall be taken within three business days from the date of receipt of all or part of the payment. At this time, "Mall" takes appropriate measures to help users check the supply procedures and progress of goods, etc.\n② "Mall" specifies the means of delivery, the person who bears the shipping cost by means, and the delivery period by means for the goods purchased by the user. If the "mall" exceeds the agreed delivery period, the user shall be compensated for the damage caused by it. But "mol" is intentional.This is not the case if you have proved that you are not culpable.\nArticle 14 (Refund)\n"Mall" shall notify the user of the reason without delay if the goods, etc. requested by the user cannot be delivered or provided due to out of stock, etc., and if the payment is received in advance, refund or take necessary measures for refund within three business days.\nArticle 15 (Revocation of subscription, etc.)\n① A user who has signed a contract with "Mall" on the purchase of goods, etc. may withdraw the subscription within seven days from the date of receipt of a written contract under Article 13 (2) of the Consumer Protection Act in Electronic Commerce, etc. (if the supply of goods, etc. is later than the time of receipt). However, if the withdrawal of subscription is otherwise stipulated in the Consumer Protection Act in Electronic Commerce, etc., the provisions of the same Act shall be followed.\n② When a user receives goods, etc., he/she shall not return or exchange goods in any of the following cases:\n1. Where goods, etc. are lost or damaged due to reasons responsible to the user (However, if the packaging, etc. is damaged to check the contents of goods, etc., the subscription may be withdrawn.)\n2. Where the value of goods, etc. has significantly decreased due to user use or partial consumption.\n3. Where the value of goods, etc. has decreased significantly to the extent that it is difficult to resell over time.\n4. Where the packaging of the original goods, etc. is damaged when reproduction is possible with goods, etc. with the same performance.\n③ In the case of paragraph (2) 2 through 4, the withdrawal of subscription by users is not restricted unless "mall" has been specified in a place where consumers can easily know in advance that the withdrawal of subscription is restricted or measures such as providing trial products are taken.\n④ Notwithstanding paragraphs (1) and (2), if the contents of goods, etc. are different from the contents of the display or advertisement or are implemented differently from the contents of the contract, the user may withdraw the subscription within three months from the date of receiving the goods, etc. or within 30 days from the date of knowing such fact.\nArticle 16 (Effect of withdrawal of subscription, etc.)\n① "Mall" shall refund the amount of goods, etc. already paid within three business days when goods, etc. are returned from the user. In this case, if the "Mall" delays the refund of goods, etc. to the user, the delayed period shall be paid by multiplying the delayed interest rate (deleting the parentheses) prescribed in Article 21-2 of the Enforcement Decree of the Consumer Protection Act on Electronic Commerce, etc.\n② In refunding the above payment, "Mall" requests the business operator who provided the payment method to suspend or cancel the claim for goods, etc. without delay when the user pays for goods, etc. through a payment method such as credit card or electronic money.\n③ In the case of withdrawal of subscription, etc., the user shall bear the expenses necessary for the return of the supplied goods, etc. "Mall" does not claim a penalty or compensation for damages due to withdrawal of subscription. However, if the contents of goods, etc. are different from the contents of the display or advertisement or are implemented differently from the contents of the contract, the "Mall" shall bear the expenses required for the return of goods, etc.\n④ If the user pays the shipping cost when receiving goods, etc., "Mall" clearly indicates who pays the cost when withdrawing the subscription.\nArticle 17 (Personal Information Protection)\n① "Mall" collects minimum personal information to the extent necessary for providing services when collecting personal information of users.\n② "Mall" does not collect information necessary to fulfill the purchase contract in advance when signing up for a member. However, this is not the case when identification is required before the purchase contract in order to fulfill the obligations under related laws and regulations, and the minimum specific personal information is collected.\n③ "Mall" shall notify the relevant user of the purpose and obtain consent when collecting and using the user\'s personal information.\n④ "Mall" shall not use the collected personal information for any purpose other than the purpose, and where a new purpose of use arises or provides it to a third party, the purpose shall be notified to the relevant user and consent shall be obtained at the stage of use and provision. However, exceptions are made if the relevant laws and regulations stipulate otherwise.\n⑤ Where "Mall" requires the consent of the user pursuant to paragraphs (2) and (3), the identity of the person in charge of personal information protection (affiliation, name and phone number, other contact information), information collection and use purpose, and information provision to third parties (information to be provided) shall be withdrawn at any time.\n⑥ The user may request access and error correction of his or her personal information held by the Mall at any time, and the Mall is obligated to take necessary measures without delay. If the user requests correction of the error, "Mall" will not use the personal information until the error is corrected.\n⑦ For the protection of personal information, "Mall" shall limit the number of users who process their personal information to a minimum and shall be responsible for all damages caused by loss, theft, leakage, provision to third parties without consent, and alteration of their personal information, including credit cards and bank accounts.\n⑧ "Mall" or a third party who has received personal information from it shall destroy the personal information without delay when it achieves the purpose of collecting or receiving personal information.\n⑨ "Mall" does not set the consent column for the collection, use, or provision of personal information as selected in advance. In addition, it specifically specifies services restricted when users refuse to consent to collect, use, or provide personal information, and does not restrict or refuse to provide services such as membership registration on the grounds of the user\'s refusal to collect, use, and provide personal information.\nArticle 18 (Obligation of "Mall")\n① "Mall" does not act prohibited by laws and regulations or contrary to public order and customs, and goods are continuously and stably as prescribed by these terms and conditions.We must do our best to provide services.\n② The "Mall" shall have a security system for the protection of users\' personal information (including credit information) so that users can use the Internet service safely.\n③ "Mall" refers to goods or services.Unfair indication prescribed in Article 3 of the Act on Fair Advertising.If a user suffers damage through advertising, he or she is responsible for compensation.\n④ "Mall" does not send for-profit advertising emails that you do not want.\nArticle 19 (Obligation for ID and password of a member)\n① Except in the case of Article 17, the member is responsible for managing the ID and password.\n② Members shall not allow third parties to use their IDs and passwords.\n③ If a member recognizes that his/her ID and password have been stolen or used by a third party, he/she shall notify "Mall" immediately and follow "Mall"\'s instructions.\nArticle 20 (Obligation of Users)\nThe user shall not:\n1. Registration of false information when applying or changing\n2. Stealing information from others\n3. Change of information posted in "Mall"\n4. Transmission or posting of information (computer programs, etc.) other than information prescribed by "Mall"\n5. Infringement of intellectual property rights such as "mall" and other copyrights of third parties\n6. "Mall" or other acts that damage the reputation of third parties or interfere with their work.\n7. Disclosure or posting obscene or violent messages, images, voices, or other information contrary to public morals in the mall.\nArticle 21 (Relationship between the "mall" and the "mall" to be connected)\n① If the parent "mall" and the child "mall" are hyperlinked (such as the target of the hyperlink includes letters, pictures, and fairy tales), the former is called the linked "mall" (website), and the latter is called the connected "mall" (website).\n② The consolidated "mall" shall not be liable for guarantee of transactions with the user by goods, etc. provided by the consolidated "mall", if the initial screen of the consolidated "mall" or the pop-up screen at the time of connection.\nArticle 22 (Restriction on attribution and use of copyright)\n① Copyright and other intellectual property rights to works created by "Mall" belong to "Mall".\n② Users shall not reproduce, transmit, publish, distribute, broadcast, or allow third parties to use the information obtained by using "Mall" for commercial purposes without the prior consent of "Mall".\n③ "Mall" shall notify the user of the copyright attributed to the user in accordance with the agreement.\nArticle 23 (Dispute Resolution)\n① The "Mall" shall establish a damage compensation handling organization to reflect legitimate opinions or complaints raised by the user and compensate for the damage.It\'s in operation.\n② "Mall" handles complaints and comments submitted by users preferentially. However, if it is difficult to process quickly, we will immediately notify the user of the reason and the processing schedule.\n③ If a user applies for damage relief in connection with an e-commerce dispute between a "mall" and a user, it may be subject to mediation by the Fair Trade Commission or a dispute settlement agency commissioned by the city/provincial governor.\nArticle 24 (Judicial Rights and Applicable Acts)\n① A lawsuit concerning an e-commerce dispute between the "mall" and the user shall be subject to the address of the user at the time of filing, and if there is no address, the district court having jurisdiction over the residence shall have exclusive jurisdiction. However, if the user\'s address or residence is not clear at the time of filing the complaint, or if a foreign resident is a foreigner, it is filed with the competent court under the Civil Procedure Act.\n② Korean law applies to e-commerce lawsuits filed between "mall" and users.\nAppendix (Effective Date) These terms and conditions will take effect from the date of the year. Appendix (Effective Date) These terms and conditions will take effect from the date of the year.</string>
    <string name="email_none">This email does not exist.</string>
    <string name="order_person">an order</string>
    <string name="current_order">Order processing status</string>
    <string name="order_cancel">order cancellation</string>
    <string name="order_cancel_waiting">Waiting for order cancellation</string>
    <string name="order_cancel_finish">Order cancellation completed</string>
    <string name="terminate_condition_notice_explain">In the event of order cancellation/refund, the accumulated points for product purchase will be canceled together. When you withdraw from the membership, the reserve will automatically expire. The reserve will be extinguished even if there is no accumulation of additional reserves for three years from the date of the final reserve.</string>
    <string name="order">To place an order</string>
    <string name="detail_order">Order Details</string>
    <string name="order_notice">Order Information</string>
    <string name="warning">precautions</string>
    <string name="search_bread">Search for the bread you want to find.</string>
    <string name="search_address">Search for the address you want to find.</string>
    <string name="recent_search">Recent search terms</string>
    <string name="no_recent_address">There is no recent delivery destination.</string>
    <string name="congratulations">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancellation</string>
    <string name="order_cancel_reason">Reason for cancellation</string>
    <string name="cancel_do_it">To cancel</string>
    <string name="pay_kakao">Kakao Pay</string>
    <string name="cake">Cake</string>
    <string name="cookie">Cookies, senbei.</string>
    <string name="coupon">Coupon</string>
    <string name="add_coupon">Coupon registration</string>
    <string name="coupon_not_apply">Coupon not applied</string>
    <string name="coupon_code">Coupon code</string>
    <string name="request_coupon_code">Please enter the coupon code.</string>
    <string name="size_korean">Size</string>
    <string name="delivery_post">courier delivery</string>
    <string name="destroy_box">Damage to packaging materials</string>
    <string name="sold_out_korean">Out of stock</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="detail_agree_3">You can receive useful shopping information from the shopping mall, such as discount coupons, benefits, events, and news of new products, by SMS or e-mail.\nHowever, order/trade information and key policy related content will be sent regardless of whether you agreements are accepted or not.\nYou can register as a member even if you do not agree to the selection terms and conditions, and you can change the reception status at any time on the member information revision page after signing up.</string>
    <string name="current_order_address">Current delivery destination</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="refund">Refund</string>
    <string name="order_refund_waiting">Waiting for refund</string>
    <string name="order_refund_finish">Refund completed</string>
    <string name="order_refund_reason">Reason for refund</string>
    <string name="refund_notice_explain">If you refund, we will refund the payment within 3 business days after confirming whether you have returned the product.\nIf you paid with a credit card, cancel the credit card approval so that the payment will not be charged.\n(However, if the payment can be charged according to the credit card payment date, the credit card company will refund the payment for the next month.)</string>
    <string name="refund_notice">Refund Information</string>
    <string name="recall_do_it">Refunding</string>
    <string name="register">Sign up</string>
    <string name="register_notice">Sign up information</string>
    <string name="delete_auth">Withdrawal</string>
    <string name="write_review">Writing a review</string>
    <string name="phone">Cell phone</string>
    <string name="pay_phone">Mobile Phone Small Payment [Content]</string>
</resources>